The Internship is a action film directed by James Bamford.
A CIA-trained assassin recruits other graduates from her secret childhood
program, The Internship, to violently destroy the organization.
The CIA fights back with deadly force.
Renee, played by Lizzy Greene.
Candace Dalton, played by Megan Boone.
Apothecary, played by Sky Katz.
Dick Jones, played by Philip Winchester.
Dagger, played by Alix Villaret.
Rubicon, played by Ollie Roddy.
This is a list of American films that are scheduled for release in 2026.
Following the box office section, this list is organized chronologically, providing information
on release dates, production companies, directors, and principal cast members.
The tone is dark.